A Finding Aid to the Howard Kanovitz papers, 1953-2017, bulk 1963-1999, in the Archives of American Art.
Archives of American Art
Howard Kanovitz papers
1953-2017
bulk 1963-1999
Archives of American Art
Kanovitz, Howard
AAA.kanohowa
Archival Resource Key
8 Linear feet
1 Gigabyte
The papers of painter Howard Kanovitz measure 8.0 linear feet and 1 GB and date from 1953-2017. The collection documents Kanovitz's work as a professional artist through biographical material; personal and professional correspondence; writings; interviews; personal business records; gallery, exhibition and project files; photographic and printed material; sound and video recordings; and preliminary drawings and studies for artworks.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 11 series.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1971-2007 (0.35 linear feet; Box 4-5, 8)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1953-2007 (0.50 linear feet; Box 1)
Series 3: Writings, circa 1954-2007 (0.60 linear feet; Box 1-2)
Series 4: Exhibition Files, 1965-2008 (0.40 linear feet; Box 2)
Series 5: Gallery Files, 1969-2007 (0.70 linear feet; Box 2, 3)
Series 6: Project Files, 1974-2008 (0.40 linear feet, Box 3)
Series 7: Personal Business Records, 1936-2000 (0.30 linear feet; Box 3)
Series 8: Printed Material, 1960-2017 (1.95 linear feet; Box 4-5, 8; OV 14)
Series 9: Artwork, circa 1960s-circa1990s (0.70 linear feet; Box 5, 8, 10; OV 11-13; OV 15-18)
Series 10: Photographic Material, 1954-2008 (1.40 linear feet; Box 6-7)
Series 11: Sound Recordings and Video Recordings, 1967-2008 (0.70 linear feet; Box 7, 9)
Biographical / Historical
Howard Kanovitz (1929-2009) was a painter based in New York City and Southampton, NY. After an early career as a jazz trombonist, Kanovitz began painting in 1949 and studied at The Rhode Island School of Design and The Art Students League in Woodstock with Yasuo Kuniyoshi. He moved to New York City and apprenticed with Franz Kline. Although he began his painting career as an abstract expressionist, Kanovitz became one of the early practitioners of photorealism in the 1960s. He also taught at the Salzburger Summer Art School and the School of Visual Arts and took on set design projects in both America and Germany. Kanovitz had more than fifty one-person gallery shows, with his last in 2008, one year before he died.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Researchers interested in accessing born-digital records or audiovisual recordings in this collection must use access copies. Contact References Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated in 2021 by Carolyn Oldenbusch, Kanovitz's widow and Director of the Howard Kanovitz Foundation.
Scope and Contents
The papers of painter Howard Kanovitz measure 8.00 linear feet and 1 GB and date from 1953-2017. The collection documents Kanovitz's work as a professional artist through biographical material; personal and professional correspondence; writings; interviews; personal business records; gallery, exhibition and project files; photographic and printed material; sound and video recordings; and preliminary drawings and studies for artworks.
Biographical material includes Kanovitz's address and appointment books, artist statements, CVs, genealogical research, a Guggenheim fellowship application, and United States passports. Correspondence files reflect relationships with friends and colleagues, including Frank O'Hara, Larry Rivers, Gregory Corso, B.H. Friedman, and others, as well as curators, museums, and galleries in the United States and Europe. Writings include Kanovitz's notes and notebooks; essays, poetry, and prose by Kanovitz; lists of artworks; poems by others; manuscripts; graduate student papers; and lectures given by Kanovitz. Exhibition and gallery files include checklists, mailing lists, inventories, correspondence, contracts, commission files, invoices, sales records, and proposals related to installations that included Kanovitz's work. Project files include correspondence, artist bios, contracts, invoices, press releases, interview transcripts, notes, source material, and photographs related to film, theater, and other projects. Personal business records include bills of sale, consignment memos, invoices, price lists, and leases for art studios and apartments. Printed material includes publications; clippings; exhibition announcements and catalogs; event programs; source material; posters; and a scrapbook of digital prints. Artwork includes preliminary sketches and source material for Kanovitz's photo-based paintings and set design materials for a circa 1977 play entitled, "The Party." Photographic material includes color and black and white prints, slides, negatives, transparencies, digital prints, and contact sheets that document exhibition installations, friends, artworks, commissions, and various studies and source material. Sound and video recordings include interviews, films, BBC broadcasts, documentaries, and performances that document Kanovitz's set design.
Painters -- New York (State) -- Southampton; Painters -- New York (State) -- New York; Photo-realism; Drawings; Interviews; Sketchbooks; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Friedman, B. H. (Bernard Harper), 1926-2011; O'Hara, Frank, 1926-1966; Rivers, Larry, 1925-2002
- Biographical Material, 1971-2007; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.35 Linear feet Box 4-5, 8
  Scope and Contents
  Biographical material includes Kanovitz's personal address book and appointment books dating between 1989 and 2007; artists statements and writings about Kanovitz from 1972 to 2007, CVs and biographical notes from 1971-2007; genealogical research documenting Kanovitz's ancestory; a 1984 Guggenheim Foundation fellowship application; a 1985 East Thirteenth Street Band vinyl record featuring cover art by Larry Rivers, and two United States Passports.
  - Address Book, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Books, 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Books, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Books, 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Artist Statements and Writings Re Howard Kanovitz, 1972-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CVs and Biographical Notes Re Howard Kanovitz, 1971-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Genealogy Research, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Guggenheim Foundation Application, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The East Thirteenth Street Band Album and Album Cover, 1985; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound discs (vinyl) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - United States Passports, 1996, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1953-2007; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Box 1
  Correspondence documents Kanovitz's personal and professional relationship with artists, writers, musicians, curators, shipping and insurance companies, galleries, and museums across the world from 1953 to 2007. Materials are arranged alphabetically by name, organization, or subject matter and include correspondence, invoices, photographic material, sketches, contracts and agreements, and prices lists. Notable figures include B.H. Friedman, Frank O'Hara, Michael Zwerin, and Larry Rivers.
  - A, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Daniel Abadie, 1973-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Abbaye Saint-Andre Centre d'Art Contemporian, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Akademie Der Kunste, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Altos De Chavon Consignment Agreement, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Artwork Sales and Loans, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - John M. Balph, 1962, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - C, 1956, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Day + Meyer Storage, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Frankfurter Kunstverein Museum, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bob [B.H.] Friedman, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fund For Artists Colonies, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - G, 1989-1991, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Galerie Thomas, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Peter Gimpel, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Daniel Goldreyer, Ltd., 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Benjamin Gollay, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - H, 1972, 1977, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Hannover-Kestner-Freiburg, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hanseatische Assekuranz Insurance, 1979-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Image Reproduction Requests, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - J, 1973, 1975, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Howard Kanovitz, 1973-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Kelpra Studio, Ltd., 1969, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Wouter Kotte, 1973-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - L, 1957-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Letters and Invoices Re Framing Services, 1978-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Al Levitt, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - London Publishers, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - M, 1958-1982, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - O, 1989-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Frank O'Hara, 1954-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - P, 1959, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Print Publishers, Art Books, Exhibitions, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Yan Proton, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - R, 1957-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Larry Rivers, 1953-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Rothman's of Pall Mall Canada, Ltd., 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - S, 1958-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - School of Visual Arts, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Sennelier, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Southampton College, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - T, 1973-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - The Jewish Musem, Gift of "Study for a Purim Crown", 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - W, 1967-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Wilhem Lehmbruck Museum, 1974-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - W. R. Keating + Company, 1979, 1980, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Y, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Michael Zwerin, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Writings, circa 1954-2007; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.6 Linear feet Box 1-2
  Writings include final copies of graduate student papers, theses, and proposals about Howard Kanovitz dated 1989, 1996, 1998, and 2007; two B.H. Friedman manuscripts dated 1988 and 1998, including "Beauty Business;" a draft statement regarding Kanovitz's painting, "Rain;" essays, poetry, and prose written by Kanovitz between the circa 1950s and circa 1970s; loose notes; a circa 1990s notebook; a list of artwork; copies of poems by Frank O'Hara, Walt Whitman, and Jeni Olan; Southampton Artists' Association lecture, lecture slides, and sound recording dated 1989 and 1995; transcripts from a 1996 event, "Friday Night Panels, Photographs and Paintings;" and a circa 1969 essay by Udo Kultermansa, "Howard Kanovitz and Tradition."
  - Bob [B.H.] Friedman Manuscript [1], 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Bob [B.H.] Friedman Manuscript [2], 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bob [B.H.] Friedman Manuscript, "Beauty Business", 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Draft Statement Re "Rain" Painting, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Essays and Poems by Howard Kanovitz, circa 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Essays Re Howard Kanovitz, 1971, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - From Abstract Expressionism to Computer Imaging: An Overview of the Work of Howard Kanovitz, A Talk Presented by Carolyn Oldenbusch, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Howard Kanovitz: A Conceptual Realist, Thesis Submitted by Karin Lukas, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Howard Kanovitz: Ein Konzeptueller Realist, MA Thesis, Karin Lukas, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - List of Artwork, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Notes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photo-Realism Re-Examined: Howard Kanovitz's Multiple Realities, A Dissertation Proposal Presented by Carolyn Oldenbusch, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Poems by Frank O'Hara and Walt Whitman, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Poems by Jeni Olan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Poetry/Prose by Howard Kanovitz, circa 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Southampton Artists' Association Lecture and Lecture Slides [1], 1995, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Southampton Artists' Association Lecture Sound Recordings [2], 1995, 1989; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Stylistic Evolution in the Art of Howard Kanovitz, Student Paper, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts: "Friday Night Panels: Photographs and Paintings" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Udo Kultermansa, "Howard Kanovitz and Tradition", circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Exhibition Files, 1965-2008; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Box 2
  Exhibition files include planning documentation from various solo and group exhibitions between 1965 and 2008. Materials include proposals, checklists, invoices, announcements, correspondence, consignment agreements, contracts, shipping documentation, clippings, press releases, and photographic material. Also included are three mailing lists for Kanovitz's European and United States contacts. Exhibitions of note include the 1966 Jewish Museum show, "Howard Kanovitz: Recent Paintings and Drawings."
  - Checklist Proposal for Folkwang, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mailing Lists, Europe, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mailing Lists, Parties, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mailing Lists, United States, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Windows, Doors and Walls, Works by Howard Kanovitz, an Exhibition Proposal, 1965-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "Wie Es War" Installation Diagram and Transparencies, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Howard Kanovitz: Paintings and Drawings Selected from the Years 1953-1964 (1964), 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Howard Kanovitz: Recent Paintings and Drawings (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Artists in the Theater (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Automobile and Culture (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Works of the Sea (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Picturing the Modern Amazon (2000), 1993, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "In Memory of My Feelings:" Frank O'Hara and American Art (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Painting Through the Lens (2008), 2000, 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Gallery Files, 1969-2007; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 0.7 Linear feet Box 2, 3
  Gallery files document Kanovitz's long professional relationship with art galleries in the U.S. and Europe between 1969 and 2007. Materials include checklists, clippings, correspondence, invoices, inventories, consignment agreements, contracts, shipping documentation, sales and price lists, photographic material, contact lists, announcements, and notes. Galleries of note include Marlborough Gallery in New York City and Galerie Inge Baecker in Germany.
  - Angela Flowers Gallery, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Arlene Bujese Gallery/Benton Gallery, 1986-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Clarkfine Art, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - DAAD Gallery, 1978-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Elaine Benson Gallery, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, 1999-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, Checklists, 1999-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Galerie Inge Baecker, Inventories, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Galerie Jollenbech/Galerie M. E. Thelen [1], 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Galerie Jollenbech/Galerie M. E. Thelen [2], 1969-1974, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Galerie Ostergren, 1969-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Galerie Ulrich Gering, 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Louise Himelfarb Gallery, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Marlborough Gallery, Checklists, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Marlborough Gallery, Contracts, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Marlborough Gallery, Consignments, 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Marlborough Gallery, Correspondence, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Marlborough Gallery, Sales, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Nabi Gallery, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Stefanotty Gallery, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Vered Gallery, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Project Files, 1974-2008; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Box 3
  Project files document Kanovitz's film collaborations, set design work, commissions, and website. Film collaborations include "Hampton's Drive-In" dated 1974-1979 and "Painting the Moon," dated 1979, and are documented through correspondence, contracts, press releases, and invoices. Website material includes printed emails, artists bios, notes, and clippings. Commissions include a 1990s mural project in Berlin, the 1987 Southeby's collector's wall, a 1972 interview with Peter Sanger regarding New Realism, and two theater projects, "Artists in the Theater," "Artists and Poets in the Theater," and "Die Bakchen." Theater project materials date between 1974 and 2008 and include photographic material, correspondence, transcripts, and clippings.
  - Artists in the Theater and Artists and Poets in the Theater, 1977-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Berliners"-Working Title, Mural Project, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Die Bakchen, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Film, "Hampton Drive-In", 1974-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Film, "Painting the Moon", 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Howard Kanovitz Website, 1998, 2000-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Peter Sager Interview Re New Realism, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Southeby-Collector's Wall, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Personal Business Records, 1963-2000; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.3 Linear feet Box 3
  Personal business records include bills of sale for Kanovtiz's artwork between 1982 and 1983; consignment memos between 1986 and 2006; price lists from the circa 1960s to circa 1980s; invoices related to 1978 reproductions of Gershwin portraits; and leases dating between 1963-1968 for 122 Second Avenue, 356 Bowery, 461-463 Broome Street, and Kanovitz's Chadwick studio in London.
  - Bills of Sale, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Consignment Memos, 1986-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Invoices Re Gershwin Portraits Reproductions, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Leases, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Leases, 122 Second Avenue, 1963-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Leases, 356 Bowery, 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Leases, BRAC 461-463 Broome Street, 1976-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Leases, Chadwick Studio, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Price Lists, circa 1960s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Printed Material, 1960-2017; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 1.95 Linear feet Box 4-5, 8; OV 14
  Printed material includes publications annotated and inscribed by Kanovitz's friends and colleagues; reviews and other clippings; clippings related to artist friends and the play, "Sheila;" source material for the 1971 exhibition, "Death in Treme;" group and solo exhibition announcements and catalogs from 1969 to 2017; magazines featuring articles related to Kanovitz from 1966 to 2001; exhibition and event posters, including an East Thirteenth Street Band poster; and a scrapbook of digital prints from a circa 1999 "Works on Paper" exhibition.
  - Annotated Publications, 1975, 1980, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1965-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Clippings, 1970-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 2001-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Clippings Re Artist Friends, 1987-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Clippings Re "Sheila", 1980, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Death in Treme, Source Material, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1969-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Announcements [1], 1970-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Announcements [2], 1970-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1991-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1961, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1970, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1972, 1978, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)